Tufts Daily Records UA176
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Negatives, 1905 -- 2004; 1980 -- 2004; UA176.002; 5.0 Linear Feet
  - News and Features, Spring and Fall, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003
    - Voting for Senate, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00048; Merwise, Steve (Box 4)
    - Rev. Scotty McLennan, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00049; Benedict, Tom (Box 4)
    - Kid's Day, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00050; Merwise, Steve (Box 4)
    - Kid's Day, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00051; Adderley, Catherine (Box 4)
    - Spring Photos, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00052 (Box 4)
    - Press conference President Mayer/ Girant Curtis/ Jim Watson, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00053 (Box 4)
    - Tractor Crashing Cars, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00054; Cohn, Rick (Box 4)
    - President Jean Mayer Press Conference, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00055; Adderley, Catherine (Box 4)
    - Shanty Town, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00056; Merwise, Steve (Box 4)
    - Fire at Carmichael Hall, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00057; Adderley, Catherine (Box 4)
    - Campus Center with no Graves House., 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00058; Adderley, Catherine (Box 4)
    - El Salvador Lecture, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00059; Adderley, Catherine (Box 4)
    - Espresso's/ Pizza Place, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00060; Adderley, Catherine (Box 4)
    - Women's Most Valuable Player- Winter, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00061; Adderley, Catherine (Box 4)
    - Prof. Eichenberg, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00062; Adderley, Catherine (Box 4)
    - Students- People Walking Around, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00063; Merwise, Steve (Box 4)
    - Sanctuary: The Spirit of Harriet Tubman, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00064 (Box 4)
    - Campus Center, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00065 (Box 4)
    - Skin, MacPhie Pub Band, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00066; Braren, Paul (Box 4)
    - Scenics of Campus, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00067; Braren, Paul (Box 4)
    - Scenics, Windy Autumn, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00068; Braren, Paul (Box 4)
    - Senate, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00069; Kulukudis, Natalie (Box 4)
    - Salacuse Jeswald, Dean of Fletcher, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00070; Braren, Paul (Box 4)
    - Rally, 1986; UA176.002.004.00003.00071; Mah, Jeani (Box 4)
  - Features, Fall and Spring, 1974 -- 1993; UA176.002.005.00001
    - Tuftonia's Day, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00001; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - ACME, Science Center, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00002; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - African Music, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00003 (Box 5)
    - Amateur Radio Society, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00004; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Apple Jam, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00005; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Aquino, Corazon, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00006; Stevens, Chris (Box 5)
    - Alumni Dance, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00007; Wajszckuk, Waldek (Box 5)
    - Baker, Kathy/Student Activities Office, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00008; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Peggy Barrett, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00009; Rashid, K. (Box 5)
    - Bateman, Justine, 213 Haskell Hall, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00010; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Center for Communication, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00011; B., Julie (Box 5)
    - Best and Worst, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00012; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Best and Worst, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00013; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Blood Drive, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00014; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Bolles House: Career Planning, 1985; UA176.002.005.00001.00015; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Broome, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00016; Michaelman, Lauren (Box 5)
    - Bubs, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00017; Kulukundis, Natalie (Box 5)
    - Bubs, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00018; Kulukundis, Natalie (Box 5)
    - Buckley at B.U., 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00019; Stevens, Chris (Box 5)
    - Buildings, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00020; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00021 (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00022 (Box 5)
    - Miscellaneous, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00023 (Box 5)
    - Callahan, Shawn, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00024; O'Brien, Maureen (Box 5)
    - Campus Center/Ziggy's, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00025; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Cannon, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00026; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Cat, Black, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00027; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Choral, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00028; Kulukundis, Natalie (Box 5)
    - CIA Lecture-MacMicheals, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00029; O'Brien, Maureen (Box 5)
    - Cocaine, Stylish Drugs, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00030; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Cohen, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00031; Stevens, Chris (Box 5)
    - Dean Colcord P.R., 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00032; Stephenson, Laurie (Box 5)
    - Collective on Latin America, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00033; Kulukundis, Natalie (Box 5)
    - Commuters, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00034; Mah, Jeanie (Box 5)
    - Jarof Condos, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00035; Laurie Stephenson (Box 5)
    - Spring Break D.C., 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00036; Labouit, B. (Box 5)
    - Couples/44A Gabriela Tinocoa/ Michael Piasecki, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00037; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Couples, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00038; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - C.S.L. Meeting, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00039; Rashid, Kristina/Lesser, Adam (Box 5)
    - CSL Meeting, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00040; Michaelman, Lauren (Box 5)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00041; Wajszesuk, W. (Box 5)
    - Curtis, Grant-Dept. of Financial Aid, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00042; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Dance, Men and, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00043; Humphreys, Chris (Box 5)
    - Dance, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00044; Michaelman, Lauren (Box 5)
    - Dating, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00045; Catullo, Cynthia (Box 5)
    - Davids, Ronn, AEQ President, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00046; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Deans, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00047; Proctor, Katie (Box 5)
    - Deans Maxwell and Lundberg, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00048 (Box 5)
    - Dean of Financial Aid--Eastwood, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00049; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Demonstration, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00050; O'Brien, Maureen (Box 5)
    - Derelict T- Stop at Davis Square, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00051; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Dining Halls, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00052; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Dith Pran, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00053; Wajszezuk, W. (Box 5)
    - Domino's Pizza Men, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00054; Russo, Mark (Box 5)
    - Dorms, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00055; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Dorms (Cont'd), 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00056; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Dorms: Aerial Boston, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00057; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Dorm Assassin, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00058; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - The Dwarfs, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00059; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Eaton Comp. Lab, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00060 (Box 5)
    - Elias, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00061; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Elekoag- Turkish Ambassador., 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00062; Wajszezuk, W. (Box 5)
    - Exploration, Freshman Class, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00063; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Explosion, Pearson Chem. Lab P- 307, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00064; Stevens, Chris (Box 5)
    - Faculty Meeting, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00065; Michaelman, Lauren (Box 5)
    - Faculty OT and EN, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00066; Michaelman, Lauren (Box 5)
    - Faculty: Mullholland and Sherwin, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00067; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Fence, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00068; O'Brien, Maureen (Box 5)
    - Fires: Carpenter House, 158 Curtis, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00069; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Forum Cast of Tufts, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00070; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Float Parade, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00071; Eisenberg, Sharon (Box 5)
    - Fraternities, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00072; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Fraternities, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00073; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Freshman Dinner- Gittleman's, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00074; Wajszezuk, Waldez (Box 5)
    - Gallery II Exhibit, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00075; Wajszezuk, Waldez (Box 5)
    - Gallery II, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00076; O'Brien, Maureen (Box 5)
    - Gallery II, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00077; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Ganz Speak, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00078 (Box 5)
    - Girls Night Out, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00079; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Gittleman, SD, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00080; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Globescope, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00081 (Box 5)
    - Halloween, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00082; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Hampton, Henry, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00083; O'Brien, Maureen (Box 5)
    - Harvard University, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00084; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Man Lecturing, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00085; Rashid, Kristina (Box 5)
    - Hillside, Medford (Renovation), 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00086; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Soviet Jewry, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00087; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Jumbo the Elephant, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00088; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Homecoming Kings and Queens, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00089; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Huey Lewis and the News Fore, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00090; Wajszczuk, W. (Box 5)
    - Hug Meeting, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00091; Russo, Marte (Box 5)
    - Iguana Bugger- Melissa Werger, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00092; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Jackson Jills, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00093; Kulukunais, Natalie (Box 5)
    - Jazz, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00094; Rashid, Kristina (Box 5)
    - Joel, Billy The Bridge, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00095; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Jumbo's, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00096; Russo, Mark (Box 5)
    - Juniors Off- Campus (Powderhouse Sq.), 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00097; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Johnson, Parker, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00098; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Junk Food, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00099 (Box 5)
    - Kids Day, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00100 (Box 5)
    - Kids Day, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00101 (Box 5)
    - Kramer's Decline, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00102; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Leacock, Richard, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00103; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Library, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00104; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Masspira, Question #6, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00105; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - MaCaffrey, Megan, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00106; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Mass Pirg, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00107; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Mayer Press Conference, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00108; Rashid, Kristina (Box 5)
    - Mayer Referendum and Gittleman, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00109; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Mayer, Jean, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00110; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Mayer, President's House, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00111; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Anne McAnn, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00112; Wajszczuk, W. (Box 5)
    - McClennan, Reverend Scotty, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00113; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Joe McGinis, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00114; O'Brien, Maureen (Box 5)
    - Math II Midterm Exam, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00115; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Maffet, David V.P. of Operations, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00116; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Mountain Club, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00117; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Native Americans Lecture, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00118; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Ozone, Charmichael Hall, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00119; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Papa, Joe/ Janitor Tiberio Leal, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00120; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Papers- Daily, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00121; Stevens, Chris (Box 5)
    - Tufts Paraphanalia, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00122; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Parent's Weekend, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00123; Rashid, Kristina (Box 5)
    - Parent's Weekend, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00124; Russo, Mark (Box 5)
    - Parent's Weekend, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00125; Chee, Shera (Box 5)
    - Parent's Weekend, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00126; Lesser, Adam (Box 5)
    - Paths, Cannon and Goddard, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00127; Wajszczuk, W. (Box 5)
    - Pizza Eating Contest, See- Saw, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00128; Russo, Mark (Box 5)
    - Police Flah and Reah, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00129; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Dr. Alvin Poussaint, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00130; Kulukunais, Natalie (Box 5)
    - Porter Square, Sears Reconstruction, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00131; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Procrastination and Libraries, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00132; Wajszczuk, Waldek (Box 5)
    - Pub - Fools and New Day, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00133; Stevens, Chris (Box 5)
    - Seabrook, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00134; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Students, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00135; Sonja (Box 5)
    - Students, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00136; Chris (Box 5)
    - Students, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00137; Waldek (Box 5)
    - Spring Fling, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00138; Rashid, Kristina (Box 5)
    - Spring Fling, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00139; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Spring Fling, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00140; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Spring Fling, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00141; Wajszczuk, W. (Box 5)
    - Spring Fling, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00142; Wajszczuk, W. (Box 5)
    - Spring Fling, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00143; Wajszczuk, W. (Box 5)
    - Spring Fling, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00144; Weinkopf, Sonja (Box 5)
    - Springsteen, Bruce, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00145; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Sunshine, Joel: World Series Bet, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00146; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Synag Memorial Service, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00147; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - TCUJ, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00148; Weinkopf, Sonja (Box 5)
    - Tennenbaum, Michael, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00149; Russo, Mark (Box 5)
    - Terrorists, Lecture On, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00150; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Tie- Dyed Shirt (Mike Jaffa Entrepreneur), 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00151; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Tree, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00152; Waldek (Box 5)
    - Trustee Luncheon, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00153; Wejszczuk, W. (Box 5)
    - Tufts Aerial, 1988; UA176.002.005.00001.00154; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Tufts Club, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00155; Humphreys, Chris (Box 5)
    - Tufts Fest, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00156; Stephenson, Laurie (Box 5)
    - Tuftspeak, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00157; Finegan, Corinne (Box 5)
    - Tuftspeak, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00158; Finegan, Corinne (Box 5)
    - Tuftspeak, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00159; Finegan, Corinne (Box 5)
    - Tuftspeak, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00160; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Tuftspeak (Thanksgiving), 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00161; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Tuftspeak, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00162; Rashid, Kristina (Box 5)
    - Tuftspeak, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00163; Stephanson, Parker (Box 5)
    - Matilde Roof Concert Fluff, 1993; UA176.002.005.00001.00164 (Box 5)
    - Faculty, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00165 (Box 5)
    - Andrew Thompson; Bolles House, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00166; Haas, Tim (Box 5)
    - Students, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00167 (Box 5)
    - Activism, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00168 (Box 5)
    - LCS Tent Out, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00169; Tara (Box 5)
    - Students, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00170; Irene (Box 5)
    - Economy Lecture Pearson 112; Assig: Hayes House, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00171; Gomel, Yusuf (Box 5)
    - Campus Center, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00172 (Box 5)
    - Sigma Phi Epsilon Dry Rush, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00173; Lesser, Adam (Box 5)
    - Homecoming, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00174; Deschapelics, Michael (Box 5)
    - Raffel, Jim and Kramer, Dave; Hersch, Seymore, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00175 (Box 5)
    - Women's B-ball vs. Trinity, 1985; UA176.002.005.00001.00176; Kasch, Ed (Box 5)
    - TCV/Boycott Rally, UA176.002.005.00001.00177; Merwise, Steve (Box 5)
    - Kids Day; Relations between US and Europe Lecture, 1985; UA176.002.005.00001.00178; Knuettel, F. (Box 5)
    - Dean Pics, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00179 (Box 5)
    - Office Dominque Pounigliari; Lecture: Israel and Peace, 1985; UA176.002.005.00001.00180; Adderley; Dalov, Nick (Box 5)
    - Student Activities Staff, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00181; Adderley (Box 5)
    - NRBQ: Spring Fling, 1983; UA176.002.005.00001.00182 (Box 5)
    - Women Track; Robinson, Pearl, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00183; Nate (Box 5)
    - Professor Thompsom, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00184 (Box 5)
    - Harrez, Oscar; Bricker, Bob; Lofts, David, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00185 (Box 5)
    - Schwartz, Steve; and Maxwell; CSL, Faculty Meeting, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00186 (Box 5)
    - Campus Center; Owenstein, Mark, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00187; Stevens, N. (Box 5)
    - Senate/Prefab Sprout, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00188; Adderley, Catherine (Box 5)
    - Blood's Lecture: Wallace Terry speaker, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00189; Kathy (Box 5)
    - Stockwell, John - Exia Agent; TCU agent, 1974; UA176.002.005.00001.00190 (Box 5)
    - Deans #1, 1983; UA176.002.005.00001.00191 (Box 5)
    - Haury/Knable J. Reitman, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00192 (Box 5)
    - Senate Meeting/Dean Colcord Award, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00193; O'Brien, Maureen (Box 5)
    - Scenics, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00194; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Saltzman, Lenny as Duane Ford/Graceland, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00195; Wajszczuk, Waldek (Box 5)
    - Study Abroad, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00196 (Box 5)
    - Chapel, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00197; O'Brien, Maureen (Box 5)
    - Kramer, Ian, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00198; Weinkopf, Sonja (Box 5)
    - Senate, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00199; Labowitz, Bill (Box 5)
    - Ziggy's Meet and March, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00200; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Campus, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00201; Rashid, Kristina (Box 5)
    - TCU Senate and TCB Officers, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00202; Kulukunais, Natalie (Box 5)
    - Dean of Admissions Michael Benke, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00203; Haas, Tim (Box 5)
    - Students, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00204 (Box 5)
    - Soccer, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00205 (Box 5)
    - Tufts Speak, 1993; UA176.002.005.00001.00206 (Box 5)
    - Dean Feinlieb and Fluff, 1992; UA176.002.005.00001.00207; Anni (Box 5)
    - Senate, 1988; UA176.002.005.00001.00208; Stevens, Chris (Box 5)
    - Soccer/Fuff, 1993; UA176.002.005.00001.00209; Jen (Box 5)
    - Football/Sports, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00210; Tara (Box 5)
    - Swimming; Women's Basketball, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00211; Oliver (Box 5)
    - Nature; Objects, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00212 (Box 5)
    - Facilities; Student life, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00213 (Box 5)
    - Activities Fair and Fluff, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00214; Sofia (Box 5)
    - Football; Field Hockey, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00215; Judy and John (Box 5)
    - Senators, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00216; Tara (Box 5)
    - Lacrosse, 1993; UA176.002.005.00001.00217; Pescarmora (Peccarmon?), Sofia (Box 5)
    - Men's and Women's Lacrosse, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00218; Oliver (Box 5)
    - Greek Jam, 1993; UA176.002.005.00001.00219; Peccarmon (Pescarmora?), Sofia (Box 5)
    - Senators, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00220; Kramer, Richard (Box 5)
    - Senators, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00221; Kramer, Richard (Box 5)
    - Orientation 1989, UA176.002.005.00001.00222; Graner, Johnathan (Box 5)
    - Orientation 1989, UA176.002.005.00001.00223; Schatz, D. K. (Box 5)
    - Turner, T., 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00224; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
    - Twins, Shapiro, Solomon, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00225; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Ultimate Frisbee, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00226; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - U.S.S.R Citizen Exchange, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00227; Catullo, Cynthia (Box 5)
    - Voznesensky, A., 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00228; Wajszczuk, Waldek (Box 5)
    - W. B. G. S. Symposium, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00229; Stevens, Chris (Box 5)
    - Wessel Computer Center, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00230; Braren, Paul (Box 5)
    - Veteran's Day, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00231; Labowitz, Bill (Box 5)
    - West Hall Renovations, 1986; UA176.002.005.00001.00232; Rashid, Kristina (Box 5)
    - WMFO, 1987; UA176.002.005.00001.00233; Stevens, C. (Box 5)
  - Sports, Fall and Spring, 1905 -- 1987; UA176.002.006.00001
    - Men's Basketball vs. Curry, 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00001; Stevens, Chris (Box 6)
    - Men's Basketball, 1987; UA176.002.006.00001.00002; Wajszczuk, Waldek (Box 6)
    - Men's Basketball, 1987; UA176.002.006.00001.00003; Wajszczuk, Waldek (Box 6)
    - Amherst-Men's Basketball, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.006.00001.00004 (Box 6)
    - Men's Basketball-Amherst, 1986 -- 1987; UA176.002.006.00001.00005 (Box 6)
    - Men's Basketball, 1987; UA176.002.006.00001.00006; Lesser, Adam (Box 6)
    - Men's Basketball Tournament, 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00007; Stevens, Chris (Box 6)
    - Men's Basketball, 1987; UA176.002.006.00001.00008; Stevens, Chris (Box 6)
    - Men's Basketball, 1987; UA176.002.006.00001.00009; Stevens, Chris (Box 6)
    - Basketball (Men), 1987; UA176.002.006.00001.00010; Stevens, Chris (Box 6)
    - Men's Basketball, 1987; UA176.002.006.00001.00011; Stevens, Chris (Box 6)
    - Men's Basketball, 1987; UA176.002.006.00001.00012; Stevens, Chris (Box 6)
    - Men's Basketball vs. Curry, 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00013; Stevens, Chris (Box 6)
    - Men's Basketball Tournament, 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00014; Stevens, Chris (Box 6)
    - Men's Basketball Tournament, 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00015; Stevens, Chris; Lesser, Adamr (Box 6)
    - Women's Basketball, 1987; UA176.002.006.00001.00016; Weinkopf, Sonja (Box 6)
    - Women's Basketball, 1987; UA176.002.006.00001.00017; Weinkopf, Sonja (Box 6)
    - Women's Basketball, 1987; UA176.002.006.00001.00018; Stevens, Chris (Box 6)
    - Women's Basketball, 1987; UA176.002.006.00001.00019; Weinkopf, Sonja (Box 6)
    - Women's Basketball vs. Brandeis, 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00020; Wajszczuk, Waldek (Box 6)
    - Women's Basketball, 1987; UA176.002.006.00001.00021; Weinkopf, Sonja (Box 6)
    - Women's Basketball, 1987; UA176.002.006.00001.00022; Weinkopf, Sonja (Box 6)
    - Carzo, R., 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00023; Stevens, Chris (Box 6)
    - Charles, Head of the, 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00024; Stevens, Chris (Box 6)
    - Denegall, Chuck-Aerobics, 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00025; Baren, Paul (Box 6)
    - Field Hockey, 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00026; Lesser, Adam (Box 6)
    - Field Hockey vs. Williams, 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00027; Zerroglos, Daphne (Box 6)
    - Field Hockey vs. Bowdoin, 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00028; Kulukundis, Natalie (Box 6)
    - Field Hockey vs. Colby, 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00029; Kulukundis, Natalie (Box 6)
    - Football Scrimmage, 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00030; Stevens, Chris (Box 6)
    - Football vs. WPI, 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00031; Wajszczuk, Waldek (Box 6)
    - Football vs. WPI, 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00032; Wajszczuk, Waldek (Box 6)
    - Football vs. WPI, 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00033; Wajszczuk, Waldek (Box 6)
    - Football vs. Bowdoin, 1986; UA176.002.006.00001.00034; Wajszczuk, Waldek (Box 6)